http://www.metalunderground.com/info/privacy_statement.cfm

Metal Underground.com
Skip to main content
"some music was meant to stay underground..."
Privacy Statement
The following is the Privacy Statement of Metal Underground.com and all services included as of April 5, 2009, including any services added thereafter. Please read it carefully. This privacy statement applies specifically to Metal Underground.com. Questions regarding this statement should be directed to deathbringer (AT) metalunderground.com.
Personal Information
Metal Underground.com uses certain information from visitors to its web site to improve the online services we provide. Metal Underground.com explicitly asks when it needs information that personally identifies you ("Profile Information"). When our site users make posts to Metal Underground.com, their IP address and time of post are also stored in the case that that information is needed for proper moderation and/or resolution of user spoofing or abuse. Metal Underground.com will not disclose this information unless acting under a good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (1) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process; (2) protect and defend the rights or property of Metal Underground.com; (3) enforce the Metal Underground.com Terms of Service; or (4) act to protect the interests of its members or others.
Additionally, anonymous information such as the name of the domain from which you access our site; the date and time you access our site; the type of browser and operating system used to access our site; the pages visited; and, if you linked to our website from another website, the address of that site. This information is typically logged by most webserver software packages.
Metal Underground.com will not send you any unsolicited information, including e-mail, except in arbitration or resolution of any conflicts that may arise from the user engaging in inappropriate actions as defined by the Terms of Service (TOS).
Profile Information
Registration is required to access or use some sections of Metal Underground.com. When users register, they have the option to keep their personal information private, which causes it to not be displayed on their profile page. However, user interactions on the site may still be logged on their profile page, including but not limited to user comments, reviews, favorite bands, etc. We believe in transparency and accountability, so if you choose to interact with the site in these ways, you are accountable for your actions and may have them shown on your profile page regardless of whether you have chosen to reveal any personal information about yourself.
For those users who choose to make their profile information public, we have made the decision to not display users' full names. Only the first name and last initial are shown in conjunction with the other information provided, so that users can feel relatively safe from others looking up their personal address based on information obtained here.
Cookies
Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies can make the Web more useful by storing information about your preferences on a particular site. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and many major Web sites use them to provide useful features for their customers. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user's computer. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies. However, you may not be able to take advantage of some features on Metal Underground.com if you do so.
Additionally, in the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.
Third Party Advertising
Metal Underground.com uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. You can find more information about this practice and learn about your choices about not having this information used by these companies, here.
Privacy of Children
Safeguarding the profile information of children is extremely important. Metal Underground.com collects the minimum amount of Profile Information necessary to operate the service. A child's profile information will never be used for uses related to the site's service but not necessary to its operation (a "Secondary Use").
Policy Updates
Metal Underground.com reserves the right to update our privacy policy and/or terms of service at any time, without notice, however we do not plan to ever spam our users or sell their email addresses. That's just wrong.
Feedback
If at any time you believe that Metal Underground.com has not adhered to these principles, please notify us by e-mail at privacy (AT) metalunderground.com and we will use all commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and correct the problem.
Subscribe to our feed to get updates automatically or subscribe by email to receive a daily digest of heavy metal news.
F.A.Q.
Friend/Follow Us on...
Metal Underground.com v.4.3.12 (deployed Aug 15, 2011)
Copyright © 2000-2020 Metalunderground.com. All Rights Reserved (Copyright notice)
Execution Time ~ 0s.
